- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Oh wait, now he's crying.
- Let me call you back, okay?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
"Did you see that?
Oh my God!"
It was right behind me here.
That's where tragedy struck earlier today.
- There's been a bombing incident.
- Morning, Jane.
Cab to a crime scene?
That's very cosmopolitan of you.
- Well, my car wouldn't start.
- Well, of course it wouldn't.
How was your date
with agent Pike?
- It was okay.
- Just okay?
It went well.
Good, huh? Oh, well, that's great.
That's great. Excellent.
Hey. The hospital says
there's only one death.
He was right next to the bomb
when it went off.
- Could have been a lot worse.
- How many injuries?
Four, but only one serious.
A homeless man.
- They think he's gonna pull through.
- That's lucky.
Yeah. The eyewitnesses agree
that the bomb went off
in front of the kiosk
just after the bus pulled out
but so far, no one's been able
to I.D. a bomber.
Well, he probably got on the bus.
Did the first responders
get a list of the passengers?
A few.
It was chaos.
We're hoping to pull some
security footage from the area.
Anything you find, make sure you share it
with the joint terrorist task force.
They're gonna look at their crimes
and see if there's anything that fit
- with what we have here.
- You think this is terrorists?
- Well, we can't rule it out.
- Well, I think we can.
Someone just wanted
the dead guy dead.
- And why do you think that?
- Because he's dead.
I mean, look at this place. Bomber could
of killed a dozen people if he wanted to.
But, nope, this guy
just bumped off one.
Pretty ineffective terrorism,
if you ask me.
Would be a good way
to bury a homicide.
Nonetheless, we are gonna look at this
as a possible terrorist attack
until we have conclusive evidence
that shows us something else, okay?
Call the NSA and see if they heard
any chatter about an attack, okay?
Sir, we found pieces from the case
the charge was in when it exploded.
We also found this.
A bit strange, actually.
- What is it?
- It's blanketing material.
It appears to have been placed
above and beneath the charge.
- And why's that strange?
- It would have dampened the explosion.
Usually, a bomber wants
a bigger boom, you know? Not this one.
This device was designed to be lethal
only to someone situated right next to it.
I never saw that before.
Dead guy.
Boom.
"It's 9:00."
Did you just tell me
what time it is?
- Excuse me?
- Somebody just said the time.
- Oh. Yeah, my computer.
- "It's 9:00."
I've programmed it to announce
the time every quarter-hour.
I think it makes me
more efficient.
A regular reminder of the passage of time
seems to have a subtle but definite...
- I'll turn the volume down.
- Thank you.
It's not me.
They're testing the fire-alarm system.
They'll be working on it
for the next couple days.
Great!
We got an I.D. on the guy
who was killed by the bomb.
David Ronaldo, 47 years old,
from Hillsboro.
His family there's
been notified.
Does it confirm Jane's idea
that he was the original target?
Turns out he's connected
to an old murder.
14 years ago, a woman was killed
by a guy named Luis Cruz.
He busted into her house
and shot her.
He's been on death row
for the past 11 years.
How's Ronaldo connected?
For some reason, Ronaldo thought
Cruz was innocent.
He's been trying
to get him exonerated.
- How does that get you killed?
- You got me.
Abbott's gone down to the west Livingston
death row unit to talk to Cruz
see if he can shed some light
on the situation.
He left already?
What's the hurry?
Cruz is sentenced to be executed
in three days.
No, not David.
I'm afraid so, Mr. Cruz.
- It ain't right. There's no sense to it.
- How did you know Mr. Ronaldo?
We, uh...
We grew up together.
His folks were my... my foster parents
From the time I was 8.
David and me,
we were brothers, tight.
I should've been more like him,
like David.
He was a good student,
good son, good brother.
But I was...
I was a mess.
First narcotics arrest
was at the age of 16, right?
David would bail me out
help me get into a program or whatever.
Then I'd screw things up
and back I'd go.
Recently, he was trying to get
your conviction overturned.
He'd been working with my...
with my lawyer for years
spending his own money,
tracking down any...
Any crazy thing
that might help an appeal.
Mr. Cruz, have you heard
from him recently?
I got a message
a few days ago
saying that he... he might have
some good news
but he didn't want to say
until he was sure.
- And he never mentioned what it was?
- No.
You have any idea of problems
he may have had?
Girlfriend problems,
money issues?
Never mentioned any.
I appreciate your time.
Agent, I didn't kill that woman.
I don't expect you
to do anything.
I just need somebody
to believe me.
All the things
I've done in my life
I never killed anybody.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd just...
Just try to believe that.
Thanks.
What have we got, kids?
Found an atm with a camera
across the street from the explosion.
There's no video but it automatically
takes a still picture every second, so...
that's about a minute and a half
before it happened.
Then about 20 seconds later,
our bomber appears.
Techs confirmed that's the briefcase
the bomb was in.
- Can you enhance the image?
- I already did
but the disguise makes him
impossible to identify.
- Facial recognition can't do anything.
- That's quite the rug.
Then the mom and baby appear...
the bus pulls in,
bus pulls out
and...
- Boom!
- Whoa, whoa.
Okay, can you back it up a ways?
Before the bus pulls in?
- The briefcases... they're identical.
- Can you enlarge that?
See, I don't think
that's a coincidence.
Okay, can... can you pull up an image
before the explosion
but after the bus pulled in?
There's only one briefcase now
so the bomber
must have taken Ronaldo's.
Leaving Ronaldo
with the bomb at his feet.
So, the bomber
not only wanted Ronaldo dead
- he wanted what was in that briefcase.
- Exactly.
Look at that woman.
Can... can you back her up a bit?
You see?
She's there on purpose to distract Ronaldo
from the briefcase.
You find that woman,
you will find your bomber.
Try facial recognition.
Gina Petrocelli, open up!
- Ms. Petrocelli!
- "Yes?"
- FBI. Open the door.
- "Okay."
"I just got out of the shower.
I need a minute."
You have 30 seconds.
No problem. Just need to dry off.
What's this about, anyway?
20 seconds and we're coming in,
Ms. Petrocelli.
Okay, just...
Don't shoot or anything.
Just need to put
some pants on.
Those pants look all right to me, Gina.
- This your baby?
- Yeah.
Cute.
Gina, you've had run-ins
with the law before...
Arrests for fraud.
I think you know
this is far worse than that.
I didn't know anything
about the bomb. I swear.
No idea that was gonna happen.
You know who this is?
Yes. Absolutely.
His name is Peter Koch.
He's a private investigator.
- I help him out sometimes.
- I'll have Wylie run him.
What do you mean
"help him out"?
When there's something
he needs to get... Creatively.
- You mean illegally.
- Whatever.
Pete throws me some money.
I do what he asks me to do.
Why did he kill
David Ronaldo?
I don't know anything
about that.
All Pete told me is he needed
help snatching a briefcase.
I distract the Mark.
He makes the Grab. Easy.
Then I'm walking away,
and... boom...
I'm face down on the sidewalk,
I can't hear
people around me
are bleeding.
You think I would get into that
on purpose?
He didn't tell you
anything about it?
No. Just, uh...
That it was a big job.
He was gonna make
a lot of money.
New development.
Pete Koch is dead.
Local P.D. found Koch's body
in an alley in east Austin
about four hours ago...
gunshot to the head.
His watch and wallet were missing
so they assumed it was a robbery gone bad.
Any signs of the briefcase?
None. And we had his apartment searched.
It wasn't there, either.
I'd say that rules out robbery.
What about Gina Petrocelli?
This one, I think she's telling the truth.
She didn't know about the bomb
and she doesn't know
who hired Koch to get the briefcase.
Okay. Charge Petrocelli with conspiracy
and whatever else you can think of.
- Anything else?
- No, that's it.
Jane.
Do you know what this is?
I'm betting it's a transcript
from Luis Cruz's trial for murder.
- Good read?
- It's a little dry.
Cruz was a drug addict.
The night of the murder
he said that he was alone, using.
No one to confirm it.
The D.A. had circumstantial evidence
and a piece of Luis' clothing
with the dead woman's blood on it.
The blood clinched it.
Yes, well, blood's very easy to plant.
- Childishly easy, really.
- Yes, it is.
You don't think Cruz did it? Why?
Well, it's just a feeling
that I can't shake.
What do you think?
Well, David Ronaldo was looking
for evidence to clear Cruz.
He was killed and had
something stolen from him.
That pretty strongly suggests
that he was onto something.
Which means that,
in the next few days
the state of Texas is going
to execute an innocent man.
And once he's dead
there's very little incentive
to reopen the case...
Which the real killer knows.
So...
What are we gonna do
about all this?
Oh, well, I think I can come up
with something.
14 years ago, Luis Cruz was accused
of murdering this woman... Sarah Feinberg.
She was shot to death in her home
apparently by an intruder.
Her body was found
by her husband, Edward Feinberg.
Edward was a psychiatrist
at the university teaching hospital.
He found his wife's body
when he arrived home later that night.
Anything connecting Cruz
to the Feinbergs?
Yes.
Edward Feinberg knew Cruz
from a halfway-house drug-treatment
program that Feinberg ran.
Cruz and Feinberg
had an argument
because Cruz showed up to a therapy
session high three days before the murder.
And the D.A. claimed that that made
Cruz kill Sarah Feinberg?
- That's thin.
- What put Cruz at the murder scene?
They found a sweatshirt of Cruz's
snagged on a bush outside of the house
with Sarah Feinberg's blood
on it.
There was also gunpowder
on one sleeve.
- What about the gun?
- They didn't find it.
"It's 10:00."
- I'll turn it off.
- No worries. It's good to know.
10:00.
We believe that David Ronaldo
was murdered
because he had evidence
that would clear Luis Cruz.
We need to find out
what that was.
And because they're going
to execute Cruz in about... 50 hours
- we should hurry up.
- Boss, is there any evidence
that the cops or the prosecutors
made a mistake?
- Not that I can point to.
- And this case was fully appealed, right?
- Yes.
- Then can I ask why we're taking this on?
I don't want to sound cold
but it seems to me that the system did
what it was supposed to do.
No, it didn't.
Because Luis Cruz is innocent.
You're absolutely certain
of that?
Well, I'm not absolutely certain
of anything.
But I'm confident enough to know
that I'd like to try and help.
- That's good enough for me.
- Me too.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Fischer, Cho, work Ronaldo.
Go to his apartment,
see if you can find anything.
I'll call the governor's office
and let him know what we're up to.
Jane, Lisbon, talk to the Feinbergs.
Wylie...
just keep letting us know
what time it is.
Really? Well, we're just...
just getting here now.
I can't do anything tonight.
This case could go all hours.
Thursday's great.
Okay. Me too.
Bye, Marcus.
What?
Nothing. Nothing.
- Mr. Feinberg?
- Yes.
You're from the FBI?
Yes, I'm agent Lisbon.
This is Patrick Jane.
Come in.
- This is my wife, Mae.
- Nice to meet you.
Sit, please, sit.
Now...
What exactly are you here for? You said
on the phone it had to do with Luis Cruz.
Yes. His friend David Ronaldo was killed.
Have you ever heard of him?
- I don't think so.
- No.
And what does his death
have to do with us?
It's complicated.
Well, that's...
That's a little evasive, now, isn't it?
This is an ongoing investigation.
I'm not allowed to say more.
This is the room where
your wife was killed, right?
Yes.
- You have an office here, too.
- Yes, I see patients here.
That must be kind of weird.
You like to provoke,
now, don't you?
Classic defense mechanism.
And, yes, it was, as you say, "weird"
for some time.
But I wasn't going to let Cruz
chase me out of my own home.
Well, I'm not judging, honestly.
I'm just curious.
And I must say, I love what
you've done with the remodeling.
- Oh, we did it together.
- I detected your touch.
How long have you two
been married?
Oh, almost 11 years.
And did you know each other
at the time of the murder?
No. I was a new
graduate student then.
Edward was far too important
to notice me.
I went through a period of deep grieving
for several years after Sarah was killed.
But I pulled myself out of it
and we were fortunate enough
to, uh... find each other.
So, it was fate, huh?
Wonderful.
A couple more questions
before we go.
Have you ever considered suicide?
- No.
- And you, Mae...
Did your father go to your
high-school graduation ceremony?
No.
What does that have to do
with anything?
You'd be surprised.
Thank you for your time.
Before we go, do you think I could
just quickly use your bathroom?
Yeah, of course.
- It's through the kitchen, on your right.
- Thank you.
One last question.
Just curious...
How long before the first Mrs. Feinberg
died did you start your affair?
Fascinating method you have
if it is a method.
Mae and I did not have an affair
before my wife died.
Really? You're so careful to mention
your "deep grieving period," even now.
And, you know, this is not really the house
of someone that's sentimental...
quite the opposite.
You're very observant, Mr. Jane.
And perhaps you're right.
I do protest too much.
But I have grown weary and defensive
on the subject
- as I'm sure you might understand.
- I do, I do.
I understand that Luis Cruz
didn't kill your wife. You did.
And we're gonna prove it.
Unless you want to confess now
and save us all some time.
Now, I assumed that this was where
this was all building toward.
You're not the first to think it.
I was her husband, after all.
- But it's not true.
- Leave my husband alone.
I'd like you both
to leave now.
- Now.
- Yes. Of course, ma'am. Yes. Jane?
Ronaldo did not have much of a life
outside the Cruz case.
Guess not.
- This is weird.
- What?
Everything taped to the walls
is old except for this map.
Looks brand-new.
What's it doing here?
Got me.
Let's make sure
we take it back with us.
Hey, did Lisbon date
on the job at CBI?
Don't know.
Never asked.
Surprising to see her and Pike
hook up, huh?
Wouldn't have put
those two together.
You ever wonder
what Jane thinks about it?
- Never.
- Really? Why not?
My brain would explode.
Hey, Cho.
Does Ronaldo seem like the type
who'd go diving?
Ronaldo started taking diving
lessons about a month ago.
Diving lessons? Why?
Was he planning on going to the ocean?
- Not that we could tell.
- Well, isn't it obvious?
He was looking for the gun.
- He was?
- Sure.
Well, the police still haven't found the gun
that killed Sarah Feinberg.
This map shows all the bodies of water
within a 50-mile radius of the crime scene.
Ronaldo planned on diving them all
one by one in the hopes of finding it.
And why would he think the gun
was thrown into a body of water?
I don't know, but he did.
And that is why the killer
wanted his briefcase...
To see how far Ronaldo
had gotten with his plan.
That's a pretty desperate move
on Ronaldo's part.
I think "desperate" more or less
describes the whole situation.
Well, we got 20 hours.
What are we supposed to do?
We're right where
we want to be.
I'm gonna need some help
from Wylie
and we need to set up a security station
downstairs in the lobby.
- Why?
- Well, we are the FBI.
Shouldn't we be secure?
If we arrest Feinberg,
he has to stay here, right?
He can't just up and leave.
- Just overnight, until his arraignment.
- Overnight is perfect.
What are we arresting him for?
- Yes?
- Edward Feinberg?
- Yes.
- Special agent Cho, FBI.
You're under arrest, sir.
- For what?
- Prescription drug fraud.
We believe you've been selling pads
like this one to drug users.
- Where did you get that?
- Turn around, sir.
- Edward? What's going on?
- I don't know. Call Rich Summers.
- Have him meet me at the FBI office.
- I'll follow you.
Let the games begin.
Empty your pockets.
Take off your watch, please.
- When will I get these back?
- Tomorrow.
When you leave
for your arraignment.
Your purse and cellphone.
I'm not under arrest.
Why should I give you my purse?
- FBI policy.
- Well, that's crazy.
You're free to leave at any time.
But if you want to stay,
your purse and cellphone, please.
You should go.
The attorney's on his way.
No. Of course not.
I'm staying with you.
Step through, please.
Wait here, please.
- "It's 5:00."
- Excuse me?
Sorry. It's just...
Never mind.
You might want to cover
your ears.
Why would
I want to do that?
They're testing
the fire alarm!
It goes off twice a day,
at 9:00 and 5:00!
It's getting pretty annoying,
actually.
Agent Collins, show Mr. Feinberg
into interrogation.
Someone will be in shortly.
- Can't I go with him?
- No, I'm sorry.
You'll have to stay in the waiting room.
Come with me.
You should be comfortable
enough in here.
Bathrooms are around the corner.
I have to stay in here?
For how long?
I can show you to your own
interrogation room If you'd prefer.
No. That's fine.
Hello.
- What time is it?
- 8:17.
- Sorry to keep you waiting so long.
- Nonsense.
You kept me waiting on purpose
like you trumped up this drug charge.
Last, desperate attempt
to prove your pet theory.
You know, it must be very difficult
for people around you
the fact you can
never admit to being wrong.
Okay.
Well, let's cut to the chase,
shall we?
In 14 hours, Luis Cruz is gonna be
executed for a crime that you committed.
I know you think
you're doing the right thing.
I mean, it's always the husband, right?
- But in this case, it's not.
- So you've said.
Fine. Believe what you want.
- I didn't murder my wife.
- Yes, you did.
Then you got in your car and
you drove back to your office.
You stopped on the way
and you dumped the gun.
Now, you could have
dumped it anywhere
but you chose to dump it in a lake,
which is a good idea.
Great hiding spot.
Of course, until David Ronaldo
figured it out.
Ronaldo got your goat,
didn't he?
I don't even know
what you mean.
Well, I mean that he wasn't nearly
as clever as you
but he was determined.
His persistence really paid off
for him, didn't it?
- Well, you tell me.
- I will.
That's why you hired the private
detective Koch to keep an eye on him.
And you had him killed once
he started taking diving lessons.
Then you had Koch
go through his briefcase
to see what evidence he had
and then you killed Koch.
This is a very interesting theory.
But even if you find the gun
it's not gonna prove that I'm guilty.
Well, it's not gonna have
any fingerprints on it, of course
but it may still have
serial numbers on it
and you would be surprised
what the FBI can do with serial numbers.
And, of course, it does prove
Luis Cruz's innocence
because the timeline suggests
that there was no way
that he could dump
the gun anywhere
between your house and your office
before he was arrested.
Well, it looks like you've got
your work cut out for you now, doesn't it?
My name is Richard Summers.
I'm Mr. Feinberg's attorney.
I'll be sitting in for the rest
of the interrogation.
Well, I hope for your sake, Richard
that you're charging him by the hour
- 'cause it's gonna be a long night.
- Here's how this is gonna work.
You can keep my client here overnight
but he's not gonna speak to you.
- About anything.
- Richard...
Not about the prescription-drug matter
not about the murder case. Nothing.
- Are we clear?
- Crystal.
Now I'd like a moment alone
with my client.
Cho, you're up.
I'm gonna ask you
some questions.
You can ask anything you want.
He's not gonna answer you.
I want to hear it from him.
"Where were you on the night
of February 11, 2000?"
"I know this is hard, but I need to talk to
you about the night your wife died."
"Any little detail could help."
"But first, let's get you
something to drink"
"Let's just chat."
"How do you like U.T. next year?"
"I mean I don't know
about their running game."
Well, I hear
the cat's got your tongue.
You think you'll let something slip?
Okay.
I'm gonna ask you again.
Where were you on the night
of February 11, 2000
in between the hours
of 6:00 and 9:00 p.m.?
- Richard?
- Is this necessary?
- You know he's not gonna discuss it.
- Yes, it's necessary
because in seven hours,
a man is gonna die.
- You know what? I resent...
- Ed! Don't.
Kim, what are you doing?
You're not going to get anything
out of him tonight.
- You might as well let him rest.
- No.
- Dennis. You need to rest.
- Fine.
Don't get comfortable.
I'll be back.
I'll be turning out the lights,
Mr. Summers
but you are welcome to stay.
Only one pillow, though.
And hopefully the floor
is okay with you.
I'm sure it's been cleaned sometime
in the past year.
- Let's hope.
- Richard, you should go.
I want you rested
for my arraignment.
- Are you sure?
- I will not say another word
- until you get back. I promise.
- Good. Get some rest.
Hi, there.
I brought you this.
Is this from the FBI handbook?
Some good cop/bad cop thing?
No, it's just a pillow
and a blanket.
Do you have any idea what
you're doing to my husband?
You're asking him to relive
a very painful chapter in his life.
I think it was more painful for Sarah.
Anyway, it'll all be over soon enough.
6 1/2 hours, to be exact.
Yeah, then we'll finally have closure,
no thanks to you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I would like to get some rest.
You needn't be a martyr.
Take the pillow.
- Good morning, sleepyhead.
- What time is it?
It's a little after 9:00.
Your murderous ass
got to take a nap
while all the good guys
had to stay up all night.
- I take it you didn't find the gun.
- No.
So that gives me 40 minutes
to get you to talk.
- I want my attorney.
- We'll call him.
- But first, the truth.
- I have nothing to say.
We'll see.
"It's 9:30."
I'd like to know how much longer
you plan on keeping us here.
You're free to go at any time.
But your husband will remain in custody
until his arraignment.
Look, I know this is hard on you.
- You want a cup of coffee?
- Yes, thank you.
I'm checking in
with the dive unit.
Damn it. Tell them
they've got 30 minutes.
Nothing yet.
You're gonna talk to me!
Please. I-I want my attorney.
In the next few minutes
Luis Cruz is going to die for your crime.
Does that mean anything to you?
A man's death?
Is that all you've got?
Appeals to my sympathy?
Answer the question!
If he were innocent,
it would be a tragedy. But he's not.
He killed my wife,
my beautiful, sweet Sarah.
He deserves to die.
I look forward to it.
There you go.
Fischer.
He's not talking.
It's all over.
You called
the governor's office?
I spoke to an aide.
No go.
Without a weapon,
they're not gonna postpone.
Crap.
And he made it
abundantly clear
that once Cruz is executed,
the case is dead.
They're not gonna want to hear
one more word about it.
So, what now?
Come on.
Everyone's watching it on tv.
I'm sorry, people.
I wish this happened a different way.
Boss. Look.
We did what we could.
Congratulations.
For what?
Luis Cruz is dead.
Well, thank you for telling me.
Doesn't feel the way
you thought it would, does it?
No.
No, I thought I'd feel avenged,
or at least relieved.
Instead it's just sad.
And it doesn't bring
my wife back.
No. It doesn't.
I'm not supposed to be
talking to you.
And I don't even know
why I should want to.
- You think I'm a murderer.
- Oh, I don't know.
I know you didn't kill your wife.
I knew all along.
- What?
- Well, I strongly suspected you didn't.
And your reaction
to Cruz's death proves it.
Not the reaction of a guilty man.
- Your wife, Mae, however...
- What about Mae?
- Oh, come on.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll let you see for yourself.
This is her learning of the execution.
Well, that doesn't mean anything.
- Come on, you can see it. It's obvious.
- No, it's not obvious.
Well, if you didn't do it and Luis Cruz
didn't do it, who did it?
- Who wanted to kill your wife?
- I-I don't... I don't know.
Mae worked at the clinic, right?
Very easy for her to get a piece
of his clothing.
"She drove to your house,
shot your wife"
"and left his sweatshirt
at the scene."
"Then she dumped the gun
in the lake on the way home."
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
She knew you were never gonna
leave your wife
so she took care of it for you.
She was your student, your lover.
She idolized you. She was
obsessed, and you knew that.
But you enjoyed
the devotion.
It fed your ego
so you didn't allow yourself
to look too closely.
- And now an innocent man is dead.
- I don't believe any of this.
And she was the one
who convinced you
to keep the affair a secret
after your wife died, right?
Yes.
Why do you think she stayed here
all night last night?
To support you? No.
Because she's scared.
She wants to know
what we have.
Mr. Feinberg, we're dropping the charges
against you. You're free to go.
There's no point now.
We can't make a case.
Edward, thank God.
Edward, wait!
- Edward, what's wrong? Why are you ignor...
- Let me have the keys.
Well, what did they say?
- Edward, speak to me.
- Give me the keys!
Mae, I have a question for you
and you need to give me an honest answer.
You can ask me anything.
- Did you kill Sarah?
- What? Who told you that?
- I need to know. Was it you?
- Of course not.
I would die rather than hurt you.
I don't believe you.
- Don't say that.
- It was you.
- Edward, stop! It's not true!
- You knew I'd never leave her.
W... I lo... I love you. That doesn't mean
that I would kill the woman...
- Don't lie to me!
- Please. You're scaring me.
This is insane.
You are insane.
- You don't understand!
- Then explain it to me!
I did it for us!
- So we could be together.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
How could you have done this?
You have to believe me.
It was the only way.
And it worked. We're together.
Now that he's dead, we are safe.
There is no one looking
for the killer.
- We have weathered the...
- Don't touch me.
We have weathered the storm.
We should be celebrating.
Get out of the car!
Now!
I don't understand.
What's going on?
You're under arrest for the murder
of David Ronaldo, Sarah Feinberg
- And Peter Koch.
- But Luis Cruz killed Sarah.
- I mean, he was just executed for it.
- Well, actually, he wasn't.
But they said on the news...
it happened at 10:00.
8:30. I don't understand.
- You tricked me?
- Bingo.
You took our phones, his watch.
"We changed all the clocks
including your car and cellphones"
Actually, you woke up at 7:00.
The TV... they did that, too?
Oh, no. That was agent Wylie.
I'm not much with computers.
He took some footage from earlier
in the day and put a little banner on it.
I did, however, plant the bug
in your husband's pocket
that recorded everything
that you said in the car.
This is FBI agent Dennis Abbott.
I need to speak to the governor.
Feeling a little sleepy?
Mae Feinberg gave up
the location of the gun.
It was in a pond off of I-35.
So that's what David
was looking for?
Yes.
We wouldn't have been able
to find it without him.
He died trying to get me
out of here.
He did.
Lawyers are doing their thing.
It'll take a little while.
But this proves
you're innocent, Luis.
You'll be walking
out of here soon.
How'd it go?
Oh, well...
It's not every day
you get to tell a man
that he's getting off death row
and going home.
- It was emotional.
- I can imagine.
Oh, you're gonna like this.
We found out how Ronaldo knew
to look for the gun in a pond.
He went to a psychic.
She said she saw it
near a body of water.
Please. Come on.
How many times do I have to say it?
There's no such thing
as psychics.
And it's the oldest one
in the book.
I mean, if you think about it
most things are close to a body of water.
You're just mad
because she was right.
Even a broken clock
gets the chance to be right twice a day.
Horse pucky.
- Look at you.
- Don't start.
I'm not starting.
You look beautiful.
I hope he's taking you
someplace nice.
Cloth napkins
and everything.
Fancy.
Well, you have a great time.
Good night, Jane.
Night, Teresa.